Guide to the Central Washington University Office of the President, Jerilyn S, McIntyre Papers 1992-2010 (bulk 2000-2008)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Meeting Notes, VIII
  - University relations issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-10)
  - University relations issues, 2004 (Box-folder 31-11)
  - University relations issues, 2004 (Box-folder 32-1)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-2)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-3)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-4)
  - Alumni issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-5)
  - ASCWU-BOD issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-6)
  - Athletics issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-7)
  - Athletics issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-8)
  - Athletics issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-9)
  - Budget Office issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-10)
  - Business affairs issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-11)
  - Business affairs issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-12)
  - Business affairs issues, 2005 (Box-folder 32-13)
  - Cabinet issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-1)
  - Cabinet issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-2)
  - Diversity Council issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-3)
  - Equal opportunity issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-4)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-5)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-6)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-7)
  - Faculty Senate issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-8)
  - Government relations issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-9)
  - Government relations issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-10)
  - Ombuds Office issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-11)
  - President’s Office issues, 2005 (Box-folder 33-12)
  - President’s Office issues, 2005 (Box-folder 34-1)
  - Student affairs issues, 2005 (Box-folder 34-2)
  - Student affairs issues, 2005 (Box-folder 34-3)
  - Student affairs issues, 2005 (Box-folder 34-4)
  - Student trustee issues, 2005 (Box-folder 34-5)
  - University relations issues, 2005 (Box-folder 34-6)
  - University relations issues, 2005 (Box-folder 34-7)
  - University relations issues, 2005 (Box-folder 34-8)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 34-9)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 34-10)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-1)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-2)
  - ASCWU-BOD issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-3)
  - Athletics issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-4)
  - Athletics issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-5)
  - Budget Office issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-6)
  - Business affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-7)
  - Business affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-8)
  - Business affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-9)
  - Diversity Council issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-10)
  - Equal opportunity issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-11)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2006 (Box-folder 35-12)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-1)
  - Executive Assistant issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-2)
  - Faculty Senate issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-3)
  - Government relations issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-4)
  - Government relations issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-5)
  - Government relations issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-6)
  - Internal audit issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-7)
  - Ombuds Office issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-8)
  - President’s Office issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-9)
  - President’s Office issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-10)
  - Student affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-11)
  - Student affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-12)
  - Student affairs issues, 2006 (Box-folder 36-13)
  - University relations issues, 2006 (Box-folder 37-1)
  - University relations issues, 2006 (Box-folder 37-2)
  - University relations issues, 2006 (Box-folder 37-3)
  - Comprehensive campaign, 2006-2010 (Box-folder 37-4)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2007 (Box-folder 37-5)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2007 (Box-folder 37-6)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2007 (Box-folder 37-7)
  - Alumni issues, 2007 (Box-folder 37-8)
  - ASCWU-BOD issues, 2007 (Box-folder 37-9)
  - Athletics issues, 2007 (Box-folder 37-10)
  - Athletics issues, 2007 (Box-folder 37-11)
  - Budget Office issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-1)
  - Business affairs issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-2)
  - Business affairs issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-3)
  - Business affairs issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-4)
  - Cabinet issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-5)
  - Chief Planning Officer issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-6)
  - Chief Planning Officer issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-7)
  - Diversity Council issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-8)
  - Equal opportunity issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-9)
  - Faculty Senate issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-10)
  - Future of Life Sciences, 2007 (Box-folder 38-11)
  - Government relations issues, 2007 (Box-folder 38-12)
  - Government relations issues, 2007 (Box-folder 39-1)
  - Internal audit issues, 2007 (Box-folder 39-2)
  - Julie Cloninger Campaign issues, 2007 (Box-folder 39-3)
  - Ombuds Office issues, 2007 (Box-folder 39-4)
  - President’s Office issues, 2007 (Box-folder 39-5)
  - Student affairs issues, 2007 (Box-folder 39-6)
  - Student affairs issues, 2007 (Box-folder 39-7)
  - University relations issues, 2007 (Box-folder 39-8)
  - ASCWU-BOD issues, 2008 (Box-folder 39-9)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2008 (Box-folder 39-10)
  - Academic affairs issues, 2008 (Box-folder 39-11)
  - Athletic affairs issues, 2008 (Box-folder 39-12)
  - Business affairs issues, 2008 (Box-folder 40-1)
  - Business affairs issues, 2008 (Box-folder 40-2)
  - Cabinet issues, 2008 (Box-folder 40-3)
  - Chief Planning Officer issues, 2008 (Box-folder 40-4)
  - Chief Planning Officer issues, 2008 (Box-folder 40-5)
  - Chief Planning Officer issues, 2008 (Box-folder 40-6)
  - Diversity Council issues, 2008 (Box-folder 40-7)
  - Faculty Senate issues, 2008 (Box-folder 40-8)
  - Government relations issues, 2008 (Box-folder 41-1)
  - Jen Gray Campaign issues, 2008 (Box-folder 41-2)
  - Ombuds Office issues, 2008 (Box-folder 41-3)
  - President’s Office issues, 2008 (Box-folder 41-4)
  - Student affairs issues, 2008 (Box-folder 41-5)
  - Student affairs issues, 2008 (Box-folder 41-6)
  - University relations issues, 2008 (Box-folder 41-7)
  - University relations issues, 2008 (Box-folder 41-8)
- Retirement, IX
  - Announcement, 2008 (Box-folder 42-1)
  - Budget, 2008 (Box-folder 42-2)
  - Cards and letters, 2008 (Box-folder 42-3)
  - Committee meetings, 2008 (Box-folder 42-4)
  - Ellensburg gala, 2008 (Box-folder 42-5)
  - Ellensburg reception, 2008 (Box-folder 42-6)
  - Events, 2008 (Box-folder 42-7)
  - News and publicity, 2008 (Box-folder 42-8)
  - Public Records Request, 2008 (Box-folder 42-9)
  - Publicity plan, 2008 (Box-folder 42-10)
  - Video, 2008 (Box-folder 42-11)
  - Westside Reception, 2008 (Box-folder 42-12)
- Scrapbooks, X
  - News clippings, 2000 (Box-folder 42-13)
  - News clippings, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 42-14)
  - Photos and ephemera, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 43-1)
  - Photos and ephemera, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 43-2)
  - Photos and ephemera, circa 2008 (Box-folder 43-3)
  - Photos and ephemera (Box-folder 43-4)
  - Photos and ephemera (Box-folder 43-5)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book I, 2001 (Box-folder 43-6)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book I, 2000 (Box-folder 43-7)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book I, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 43-8)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book II, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 44-1)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book II, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 44-2)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book II, 2001 (Box-folder 44-3)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book II, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 44-4)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book III, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 44-5)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book III, 2003 (Box-folder 44-6)
  - Presidential Speeches, Book III, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 44-7)
- Media Materials, XI
  - Guide to CD photos, circa 2000s (Box-item 44-8)
  - Camcorder videocassette—Brown’s greeting (Box-item 45-1)
  - Camcorder videocassette—J-Mom speech, UNLV, circa 2008 (Box-item 45-2)
  - Camcorder videocassette—Karen Morse (Box-item 45-3)
  - Camcorder videocassette—Pershing’s greeting, 2008 (Box-item 45-4)
  - Cassette tapes—President Jerilyn McIntyre (3 tapes) (Box-item 45-5)
  - CD—Photos from Presidency of Jerilyn S, McIntyre, 2000-2008 (Box-item 45-6)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, October 2, 2005 (Box-item 45-7)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, December 2, 2005 (Box-item 45-8)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, May 5-6, 2006 (Box-item 45-9)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, May 6, 2006 (Box-item 45-10)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, October 6, 2006 (Box-item 45-11)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, December 8, 2006 (Box-item 45-12)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, February 2, 2007 (Box-item 45-13)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, March 2, 2007 (Box-item 45-14)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, March 2, 2007 (Box-item 45-15)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, May 4, 2007 (Box-item 45-16)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, May 4, 2007 (Box-item 45-17)
  - DVD—Board of Trustees meeting, June 8, 2009 (Box-item 45-18)
  - DVD—CWU Budget presentation to Washington Higher Education Coordinating Board, 2008 (Box-item 45-19)
  - DVD—CWU Farewell (4 copies), 2008 (Box-item 45-20)
  - DVD—Washington State House Resolution recognizing President McIntyre, 2009 (Box-item 45-21)
  - Videocassette—Board of Trustees meeting, February 4, 2005 (Box-item 45-22)
  - Videocassette—Board of Trustees meeting, May 6, 2005 (Box-item 45-23)
  - Videocassette—Board of Trustees meeting, June 10, 2005 (Box-item 45-24)
  - Videocassette—Board of Trustees meeting, October 6, 2005 (Box-item 45-25)
  - Videocassette—Board of Trustees meeting, October 7, 2005 (Box-item 45-26)
  - Videocassette—Board of Trustees meeting, December 2, 2005 (Box-item 45-27)
  - Videocassette—Board of Trustees meeting, February 3, 2006 (Box-item 45-28)
  - Videocassette—Introduction of President Jerilyn McIntyre, 2000 (Box-item 45-29)